#### Contact

bilalarslan11@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/bilal-arslan-23199057 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Software Development C#

Languages

.NET

Danish (Native or Bilingual)
Turkish (Limited Working)
English (Full Professional)

### Certifications

MS: Programming in HTML5 with JavaScript and CSS3

MS: Architecting Microsoft Azure Solutions

MCPS: Microsoft Certified Professional

# Bilal Arslan

Senior Developer at Pointsharp

Farum, Capital Region of Denmark, Denmark

# Summary

I am a software developer who combines dedication and discipline in my work, a practice that has contributed to my successful career. Balancing work and personal responsibilities, I have honed a strong sense of duty and organization. My career has been characterized by a willingness to embrace challenges and a commitment to seeing them through.

#### Education:

- Master's Degree in Computer Science, specialised in Digital Media Engineering
- Focus: Development of digital games, with an emphasis on applying software engineering principles in the gaming domain.
- Bachelor's Degree in Software Technology
- Focus: Broad range of software development techniques.
- Programming Skills: Adaptability in various programming languages, backed by a solid understanding of core programming principles.

## Experience

Pointsharp Senior Developer August 2014 - Present (10 years 11 months) Copenhagen, Capital Region, Denmark

2ndC A/S Graduate-developer August 2014 - October 2014 (3 months)

SYBO Games Internship October 2013 - October 2013 (1 month) SYBO Games, creators behind Subway Surfers. Part of the graduation of DADIU for my Competence Project. Mainly worked on prototyping and gameplay programming.

# Education

**Technical University of Denmark** 

Master of Science (M.Sc.), Digital Media Engineering · (2012 - 2014)

#### **DADIU**

Programmer, Computer Games and Programming Skills · (2013 - 2013)

Technical University of Denmark

Bachelor of Science (B.Sc.), Computer Software Engineering · (2009 - 2012)

Selandia - Højere Teknisk Eksamen

Mathematics and Physics · (2006 - 2009)

Nørrevangsskolen

· (1996 - 2006)